If we could make this quick.
如果我们能快点的话
- Shall we? - Be my guest.
- 开始吗 - 请便
Is today Friday?
今天是星期五吗
Yes.
是的
Do you reside in the United Kingdom?
你居住在英国吗
Is Frederick Alan Smalls your true legal name?
弗雷德里克·艾伦·斯莫尔斯是你的真实合法名字吗
Yes.
是的
Did you masturbate this morning?
你今天早上自慰了吗
Oh, good.
哦 很好
The embarrassing personal questions start early.
尴尬的私人问题来得真早
Yes or no whenever possible, please.
请尽可能回答是或否
You know, I’ve been looking forward to this.
你知道 我一直很期待这个
Did you masturbate this morning?
你今天早上自慰了吗
No.
没有
Didn’t have time.
没时间
Are you sitting down?
你是坐着的吗
Yes.
是的
Are the lights on in this room?
这个房间的灯是开着的吗
Are you now in the City of Westminster?
你现在在威斯敏斯特吗
No.
不是
Do you enjoy toast?
你喜欢大喝一杯吗
Very much.
非常喜欢
Yes or no.
是还是不是
Yes.
是的
Have you ever physically assaulted a significant other
你是否曾在争吵中对伴侣实施过
during an argument?
身体暴力
Girl, you know I have.
你知道答案的
Again, yes or no.
请回答是或否
Yes.
是
Enthusiastically.
并且很享受
Do you wear contact lenses?
你带隐形眼镜吗
Yes.
是
Do you smoke cigarettes?
抽烟吗
No.
否
Are you seated at the moment?
你现在坐着吗
Yes.
是
Is it morning or afternoon?
现在是上午还是下午
Afternoon. Can we go back to the EPQs?
下午能回到刚才的艾森克人格问卷吗
They’re more fun.
那些问题更有意思
Is your mother’s name Quiana?
琪亚娜是你母亲吗
Yes.
是
When did you first become aware of Severus?
你什么时候开始知道死危病毒的存在的
What’s Severus?
什么是死危病毒
Have you ever failed to support any child of yours?
你是不是一个失败的父亲
Uh...
额
only emotionally.
情感上失败吧
Yes or no.
是或否
Yes.
是
Were you resentful that I passed you over for the CI job?
我没给你集成工程师的工作 你是否心怀怨恨
- I’m fucking human. - Yes or no.
- 你他妈还想怎样 - 是或否
Yes.
是
Did you steal Severus as a means of getting even?
你是否为了报复偷走了死危病毒
No.
否
When did you first become aware of Severus?
你第一次知道死危病毒的存在是什么时候
About two months ago.
两个月前
How did you become aware?
你怎么知道的
Professional restrictions prevent me
出于职业限制
from answering the question.
我无法回答这个问题
How did you become aware?
你怎么知道的
Same answer.
我无法回答
Did a patient divulge the information to you?
是你的病人泄露的吗
Outside of war,
除了战争
have you ever killed another person?
你还杀过人吗
Define "war."
请你定义什么是战争
Declared or undeclared conflict between the United Kingdom
英国与其他国家或非国家行为体之间的
and another country or non-state actor.
已宣战或未宣战的冲突
No.
否
Outside of war, have you ever been
除了战争以外
in a shooting, knifing or fight
你是否经历过枪击捅伤或斗殴
where someone was seriously injured?
使人重伤的情况
Yes.
是
Have you ever betrayed your country?
你背叛过你的国家吗
No.
否
What is your relationship
你和佐伊·沃恩医生
with Dr. Zoe Vaughan?
是什么关系
Patient and social acquaintance.
她是我的病人
Would you like to take a break?
你想休息一下吗
I’m good.
我挺好的
Is your middle name Beatrice?
你的中间名是碧翠斯吗
No.
否
Please answer the question truthfully.
请如实回答问题
Is your middle name Beatrice?
你的中间名是碧翠斯吗
Yeah.
是
Are you tightening your anal sphincter muscle right now?
你在收缩你的肛门括约肌吗
Have you read Physiological Stress Response
你读过韦茅斯和库姆斯写的
and Polygraph Deception by Weymouth and Coombs?
生理应激反应与测谎欺骗吗
Cover to cover.
每一页都读了
Yes or no.
是或否
Yes.
是
Will you please release your sphincter muscle?
你能放松你的括约肌吗
Sure thing, George.
当然 乔治
Who asked you to plant the movie stub
是谁让你把电影票根
in the wastebasket in my closet?
放到我衣柜的垃圾桶里的
What?
什么
No one.
没人
How many people are you personally connected with
你跟多少知道死危病毒的人
who were aware of Severus?
有联系
That question is inappropriately operational.
这不是个好问题
How many people are you personally...
你跟多少知道…
George, you’re CI. You know I can’t answer that.
乔治 你是集成工程师 你知道我无法回答这个问题
Did you steal Severus?
是你偷窃了死危病毒吗
No.
否
Did you steal Severus for money?
你是为了钱偷窃死危病毒吗
Did you steal Severus for ideology?
你是为了意识形态问题偷窃死危病毒吗
What ideology?
什么意识形态
Did you steal Severus because of your ideology?
你是为了信仰偷窃死危病毒吗
The question assumes I stole Severus.
这个问题预设我偷窃了死危病毒
True or false: There is no God.
是或否 这里没有上帝
False.
否
How many sexual partners
过去三个月里
have you had in the last three months?
你有多少性伴侣
Two.
两个
True or false:
是非题
The greater good outweighs
更高的利益
immediate legal or ethical limits.
比直接的法律或道德限制更重要
Impossible to answer without specifics.
没有具体的信息我无法回答
Do you think you’re smarter than most people?
你觉得你比大多数人聪明吗
Georgie, I know I am.
乔治 我了解我自己
Yes or no.
是或否
Yes.
是
Would you like to come for dinner
你明天晚上愿意
at our home tomorrow evening?
来我们家吃晚饭吗
Huh?
什么
I need your help individually to figure something out.
我需要你帮忙解决一些问题
Can you come?
你能来吗
Um...
额
Yeah, sure.
没问题
Well, I had so much fun last time.
上次我玩的很开心
Yes or no.
是或否
Is this an order?
这是命令吗
We’ll expect you at 8:00.
晚上八点见
Wait, what the fuck did we just learn here?
我们刚刚到底在干吗
See you tomorrow.
明天见